(
"ai_sub_version": "3.5.2",
"generated_at": "2026-08-16T01:48:40.918088",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 9,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 18,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true,
"max_storage_gb": 18.0
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0,
"retries": 3,
"min_wait_seconds": 1.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 10.0,
"multiplier": 2.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000,
"verification_gap_seconds": 60,
"gap_verification_retries": 1,
"gap_verification_ignore_start": true,
"gap_verification_ignore_end": true
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
We’re ready to greet the world!
We're ready to greet the world!
We’re voyaging forward with courage to run toward a brand-new start
We're voyaging forward with courage to run toward a brand-new start
Let’s go live!
Let's go live!
Bridging the distance across the sea endlessly
Cheerfully meeting heart-to-heart!
Waking from a dream, swept up into a stream
I make a wish and wait for my cue—
How will we connect in this new frontier we’re journeying through?
How will we connect in this new frontier we're journeying through?
Thriving in a scene where no one’s ever been
Thriving in a scene where no one's ever been
With vibrant colors bursting like stars—
Radiant and warm; charged with energy that’s carried us this far!
Radiant and warm; charged with energy that's carried us this far!
Each new debut brings a miracle to life
Surely
We’ve gotta take that chance
We've gotta take that chance
We’re running nonstop; straight to the top, that’s right!
We're running nonstop; straight to the top, that's right!
We’re ready to change the game, a shimmering showcase creating a new place where we can shine!
We're ready to change the game, a shimmering showcase creating a new place where we can shine!
Day by day, sparkling stories will intertwine
Get ready to cross the waves, we’re voyaging forward with courage to run toward a brand-new stage
Get ready to cross the waves, we're voyaging forward with courage to run toward a brand-new stage
Let’s go live!
Let's go live!
Bridging the distance across the sea endlessly, follow me and we’ll turn the page!
Bridging the distance across the sea endlessly, follow me and we'll turn the page!
Breaking through the doubt, we know we’ll figure out a way to clear each towering trial;
Breaking through the doubt, we know we'll figure out a way to clear each towering trial;
Sharing all our hopes, we can conquer any challenge with a smile!
We’ll link our hearts as we search across the globe, knowing no matter where we are, no matter how far we can be stars, let’s go!
We'll link our hearts as we search across the globe, knowing no matter where we are, no matter how far we can be stars, let's go!
I wanna chase a wish unwaveringly, playing out a grand story
Share the futures that we can see, making them reality!
Take my hand and reach for the screen, all we need are glittering dreams
Our hearts and souls, all fulfilled in the world we build!
We’re ready to seize the day, traversing the pathways, discovering highways to everywhere!
We're ready to seize the day, traversing the pathways, discovering highways to everywhere!
Step by step, gathering stories that we can share, get ready to lead the way!
With each generation, a shining sensation; a dream unfurls—let’s make friends, making a moment of history joyfully! Follow me; we’ll connect the world!
With each generation, a shining sensation; a dream unfurls—let's make friends, making a moment of history joyfully! Follow me; we'll connect the world!
I wanna chase a wish unwaveringly
Playing out a grand story
Share the futures that we can see
Making them reality!
Take my hand and reach for the screen
All we need are glittering dreams
Our hearts and souls, all fulfilled in the world we build!
We're ready to seize the day
Traversing the pathways, discovering highways to everywhere!
Step by step, gathering stories that we can share!
Get ready to lead the way, with each generation, a shining sensation, a dream unfurls, let's make friends
Taking a moment of history, joyfully, follow me
We'll connect the world!
They'll hear our song, ringing out over hills and oceans, our legend grows and continues
We'll carry on, starting now, setting hearts in motion, connecting all of the world!
Yay!
Guys!
You good? You good?
Yeah, we're good.
We're great.
Okay.
We're all in 3D other than you!
All right, let's introduce each of these beautiful ladies, starting with me, um...
Hi, I'm IRyS from Hololive English.
I'm your friendly neighborhood Nephilim representing hope.
Yay!
Konfauna! It is Ceres Fauna, your gaming, healing and idol in 3D for you today, Konfauna!
Konfauna!
Konnichiwa! It's Ouro Kronii from Hololive English, and we are here to have some awesome time, swag!
Swag!
Oh, hi! I'm Nanashi Mumei, and I'm booming in 3D, hello!
Hello! Hoomin!
What's up? It's Hakos Baelz, representing chaos from HoloEN council.
Hey yo! Your rat idol, I'm here, yeah.
We just finished singing our first song together!
It was Connect the World, Hololive English's idol song, and I'm so happy I was able to sing with all of you guys today in 3D!
That was just our first song. We still have a lot in store for you, stuff you would never expect.
Could be, many? Are you liking it so far?
It's pretty good. It's all right. You guys like it? I love it personally.
Yeah, it's great! Love, even if you just like it...
We should have smashed that like button!
Smash that like button! But don't just smash that like button, be sure to talk about what you think using the hashtag...
#CouncilRyS3D 'cause we want to hear your thoughts, man!
Use the hashtag, use the hashtag. The hashtag might be #CouncilRyS3D.
All of...
What? That might not matter too much anymore.
What? Because IRyS here with these lovely, lovely, lovely CouncilLadies...
The five of us will be forming a new official unit called... Hololive English Promise!
We promise you an amazing time!
Celebration of our newly formed official unit, Hololive Promise. Today, we're going to promise to sing many songs, play many games, and celebrate being together in 3D! You guys ready?
Okay.
Well we're going to go get ready and start off with the first games. Everybody, exit stage right!
Well, we're going to get ready and start off with the first games. Everybody, exit stage right!
Yaaay! Welcome everyone, to the Promise Games!
Now, well, you know, since IRyS has joined us to create Promise, we present you with the Promise Games.
We're going to figure out who's really on top, number one.
I promise you, I'll be first, number one.
I promise you, I'll be first.
I promise you, she'll be first.
I'm going to be the top.
I promise you... not bottom?
Someone will be first.
Someone will be bottom.
We're going to battle through different games today!
And whoever has the most points at the end will be the champion of said Promise Games.
Everyone okay? Yeah!
So, if we're okay, IRyS, would you like to explain the very first game that we're going to play today?
All righty!
So first game will be... Everyone knows this game? Red light, Green light!
Now, look behind you, everyone.
Actually, no, look in front of you, everyone! Look, look what's in front of us right now!
Look at this beautiful obstacles course! Yes!
Look at this beautiful obstacle course! Yes!
This isn't just your regular Red Light, Green Light.
Whoever can avoid the obstacles and touch the goal, which is... oh, we already... the goal?
The goal, yes! The goal will earn one point!
Okay, and if you're caught by the Oni, you'll have to stay on the course and crawl for the rest of the round.
Oh. And you don't just... you don't just crawl, you can... you can babu babu and...
People who are still in the game, yes. All right, so let's go through the details of the course.
First is the balance beam. Pass this obstacle by crossing over without falling!
And after that, there is the bar, the limbo bar. You pass this obstacle by crossing under the bar limbo-style!
And after the limbo, we have the tires! You pass this obstacle by jumping across using the tires with one leg. You hop, hop, ok? Hop, hop!
And we have a special guest today to play the part of the Oni!
Oh!
Yes! Let's introduce her! Here she is!
Hello! Why are you so close? I'm so close here!
Unless my power goes over overtime... I can't keep her moving forever!
Anyway, congratulations on your sleep, D-Y-E-S... D-Y... and thank you for inviting me, Bae!
Today, I'm just strict... Skelly Oni!
Oh no! We're in trouble! Your look is very... strict, Skelly... Wait, you look very... Yeah, I want to rest on my couch. I want to sit. No, no, no, sit... Sit on the Oni's flat!
Bumpers me! Well, we have this very cute Oni here today!
Thank you! Yes!
So, is everyone ready to play? Yes! Okay! Let's get Red Light, Green Light started!
We decided on the orders beforehand with rock-paper-scissors.
Oh yes, you did! Everyone? Yes, we won, I want...
All righty! Are we ready? Yes, we play, we play! Okay, ready? Set! Go!
Green light! Red light! Green light! Red light!
IRyS out! Okay.
Green light! Red light! Green light!
I found out!
I'm so suspect today.
Please, babushka! Please, babushka!
How come you are so...
Oh, you were so... so weird, IRyS!
I'm not ready! Red light!
Green light!
Red light! Green light!
There's so many babies out there.
Mama, move me!
Red right! Ah!
Red light! Ah!
Green light!
Babushka, babushka...
I'm doing square. Oh, she's listening.
She's okay.
Red right!
Red light!
Tokino Sora!
I win! I win!
Already... Since we all didn't make it, we're doing one more!
Already... Since we all didn't make it,
we're doing one more!
We're doing one more!
One more! Okay, keep it up, keep it up.
Three rounds this time. Want to switch orders?
It's so easy, girl.
We go same order. Same order?
Same order? Okay. All right.
Okay. Are you ready? Ready?
Ready! Let's go!
Green light!
Red right!
Red light!
Green light!
Red right!
Red light!
Mmm... Nothing.
Green light!
Red right!
Red light!
Mama! Mama, move me! Green light!
Red right!
Red light!
Ah, I win! Ah!
Darn it! Okay, okay.
Green light!
Appa, ga, ga! The red light got me!
Kronii! Kronii! Almost! Guh, guh.
Green light!
Red right!
Red light!
I hope you all die! Somebody help me! Baby, move!
You're most hopeless, girl!
Mama, touch me! Red light!
Green light! Green light!
Red right! Ah!
Red light! Ah!
You're gonna pay! Thank you! Darn it!
Nice game! Nice game! Nice game!
Nice game! That was amazing!
You're all doing great!
Oh my gosh! Oh my goodness!
It was... it was just a light tap. Okay, sure.
All righty, that the game is over. Congrats, Bae, for winning!
All righty, the game is over. Congrats, Bae, for winning!
Congratulations!
Wait, a lot of us crawled a lot today. Yeah.
But it's still too early to tell who's going to win the Promise games. We still have a lot more.
Very true, very true. Yes.
All righty, thank you so much, H-Chan, for being here!
Thank you so much! Touch me, touch me! Touch me!
Thank you for the next game! Bye-bye!
What a game.
I know. Oh god. I played a lot of baby day.
Yes, enough for a lifetime. All right. I never want to see that again.
Oh! All ready? All ready?
That was a lot of fun. Now, let's move on to the next game!
Yay!
Oh! We made it to the next game arena! Yay!
And I'm here to introduce the next game, which will be the Meteo Smash Challenge!
And I'm here to introduce the next game,
which will be the Meteo Smash Challenge!
Smash! But we're not the ones who will be smashing. We're in great... no, no. We're in great peril today.
Smash! But we're not the ones who will be smashing.
We're in great peril today.
But it'll be easier to show you than to tell you.
Fauna, would you please... please spread out to your designated areas?
Spread out? Okay. Spread it out, spread it out.
And from the heavens appears...
Square meteorite!
That's a meteorite!
Is everyone alive in there?
Alive! Alive! We are alive!
Still 3D!
Still 3D, not Planton, not pancake!
As long as you make it through one of these holes in the meteorites,
Anyone who avoids the meteorites all the way through earns a point!
However, the game becomes more difficult as time goes on because there'll be fewer and fewer holes.
And no sharing! No sharing your holes!
So if... If push comes to shove, we shove. We shove! Shove? Okay, got you.
All right, everybody understand? Yeah, I understand.
All right, let's start! Ready? Everybody ready?
How many times is this meteorite going to land on us?
It's viciously square meteorites.
Goodbye! Goodbye! Goodbye!
I'm sorry! Oh God! You just have to stand there with three hands.
Everyone safe? Everyone safe? Okay.
Oh, oopsy!
Tank! Tank, tank, tank! I want some maple syrup!
I see you, Kronii.
Wait, you're alive? Wait, I'm alive?
I'm alive! Kronii's alive! She's not dead! She's dead!
All ready? Let's go!
Wait, Fauna doesn't move!
Fauna wins by doing absolutely nothing. We'll see about that!
Everybody, you made it! You made it! Oh no! Oh no! You didn't make it!
Meteor was too fast! I was squished!
Kronii died! Kronii died! Look, we have a winner. Kronii!
I think we can do one more game. One more game? Yeah, let's do that.
Can we... Are we revived? Can we... Yeah, we revive! We live!
All right, one more game. Point on the board for Kronii.
I'm sorry! It was too quick!
You tried to push me!
No, this means nature! Ha! At least I'm not the first one.
Oh, nice! Oh, no! Oh, no! Make it! I made it!
That was a nice break. I feel like pushing again.
Well, looks like someone's going to get... Kill! Kill! Kill!
I'm bald! I'm surprised I won that push. It's because I tripped.
I'm ready.
I shouldn't...
Wait, is this done? Oh, it's done!
Okay, I'm good. Oh, you...
Oh, this is why women's targets are like...
I made a grave mistake!
Oh, hello.
You should have gone for me!
Oh, this is easy. This is scary.
Honey is scary. No!
It was so close!
Oh, easy.
I don't even have to move, honestly.
What? You moved? What?
It's strategy!
It's strategy.
Strategy!
Okay. Okay.
Okay. Okay. Okay. Okay.
Are we good? Are we good?
All right. What's next?
That's pet, I'm ready.
I'm ready for some sabotage.
Sabotage.
Ready for some sabotage.
I am not hearing you.
I hear nothing.
Fight!
Fight! Fight! Fight!
Fight! Fight! Fight! Fight! Fight! Fight!
Now you're out!
What?
Red!
Oh, I'm sorry everyone.
Kronii, you're cruel!
You're strong!
Thank you everyone.
Push me from behind.
I'd like to let everyone come in again.
My goodness!
I'm sorry!
The voices! The voices were just so tempting!
This was a huge...
This was easy to push.
This was a huge game for Kronii. She's now in the lead with two points!
Two points! Oh, my god! Bae is just behind with one point!
And with that, I believe we're ready for our next game.
Next game! Next game!
Next game!
Next game! Let's go!
Okay, so the next game is Avoid the Void Challenge!
Avoid the Void!
Yeah, well, um... I think you might already know if you take a look at the stage.
Yeah!
This looks... Is this really okay?
Finders keepers. I'm just kidding. No, no, no. Just use your imagination.
So for each step, you have to pick either the left or the right asteroid, and if you pick the wrong one, you'll fall down.
And it's going to be pretty hard. Yeah, it's going to be pretty hard to reach the goal without falling...
...so you can try again until you make it.
Ah, okay.
Yeah, we don't die! We don't die!
Kids! Dammit, I didn't want the risk, you know.
Next time. Next time. Promise, we promise! Yes, promise!
So the person with the most points goes first, which is me. And the rest of you guys are going to go after me, yes.
The highest points, lowest... I go third 'cause I'm confident! Rock paper scissors! Rock paper scissors! I'm confident!
And then me! I got second place! And I won the rock paper scissors 'cause I'm just lucky like that, and I go last, yes.
Most advantage because of that. Lucky you.
All right. Well, I guess... I guess I got to start. Yeah, we're starting. Let's go!
Okay, we're right into it. Jump right in! Jump right in! But think about it, a little bit, you know.
Don't think about it.
Go with your instinct. I feel very good. I think... I think it's the left one.
Yep. Oh. Oh, yeah.
Never mind.
Oh, that was a shame.
That was a shame.
What does that mean?
Okay.
Is your turn.
Okay, my turn, my turn.
Is your turn, Bae?
Oh, you're back. Hi.
Oh, why are you back?
Yeah. Why? What are you doing?
You don't like you don't want me to be back?
No!
We want you!
Of course we want you back.
All right.
All right. Ladies?
Okay.
Bae.
So, who's on first?
Uh-huh.
Okay. Uh-huh.
See?
Who?
Uh, did she safe? Was safe?
Safe? Oh, safe!
Safe! Safe! Safe!
She should go after her. She should probably, we should, uh...
You should probably start... start walking.
Right ahead.
Mind games, the mind games.
They wouldn't do another zig, you know.
Oh.
Mind games, the mind games.
Wait, go! Go!
Okay, okay.
Wait, why are you following me?
That's weird!
Okay, that's weird.
We don't go one at a time.
Oh, wow! She lucky!
Why she lucky?
She's so red!
Okay, she's lucky.
I don't mind it.
Lead the way.
Lead the way, Bae.
There's so a lot of pressure.
Guide us. Guide us. You're the leader.
Let's go.
You need the mathematical meme that's going through my head right now.
Goal!
Ah!
No!
I know where to go.
I know what I must do.
Think about it. Think about it.
Think about it.
Okay, I really have to think hard about this next one.
You don't need to think about it!
You don't need to think about it! Just...
Just simple.
You'll slip.
Oh, no. Wait, now I know how it feels.
Now you know you think about it.
We're waiting!
Oh, no!
Oh, no, no, no, no.
Oh! Oh, I'm not...
Just think about it.
Just think if I should jump or not.
Got to think before you jump.
Just go.
I'm waiting. All right, I go.
Okay. All right?
My thinking is good.
I hate this.
Okay.
I'm going.
I don't want to be friend. I don't mean friend. Survive as long as possible until the last.
I'm going to...
She's safe! Okay.
I'm safe, I'm safe. Nice luck, Mumei.
Right behind you.
Now, what could it be? Could it be...
I would expect to go here.
Are you going to jump there?
Think I'm thinking.
It might be a third, third time's a charm on this side.
It might be, it might be that.
Or you want, you want me to fall.
No, no, I don't...
I don't want you to fall until we get to the end.
Until you get to the end.
Because you want me to do it, Iris.
Okay.
I think third time's a charm.
Third time's the charm.
Safe!
I knew it. I knew it.
Nice! Nice!
I knew it was here.
Okay.
Now, this is work.
This is where it would be really interesting if it was the fourth one, right?
Right?
Right? Yeah.
Yeah.
But would it be...
But would it be?
Would it be?
What's that theory?
I don't know.
My Nephilim senses are tingling and saying it's...
I think I'd be...
I don't think it's...
I don't think...
I think jump across.
I think I...
I just have to go here.
Okay, I just...
I'm not saying anything about my chances.
I think it's about time you start falling.
Oh, my god!
It feels so good back here, baby!
What's um...
Which one's going to be?
Are we going to regret this?
Let's see.
You got a fifty-fifty chance with me.
A fifty-fifty chance with me.
And if you fall and you fall, I get an automatic win.
Mumei!
Pick the right one.
No. No.
The right one.
No. Don't, don't, don't bring pressure.
Pressure. Pressure.
What?
The right one?
Go with your instinct.
The right one or the wrong one?
All right.
Okay. Well, we know the way.
We know the way, so we're going.
Everyone get back.
Everybody.
Okay. Oh, watch out, are you?
I make good choices.
Damn it!
You are so good!
Thank you, thank you.
It's the killer instinct.
She's got the sixth sense.
You just have to have no fear whatsoever.
No fear at all.
What's that?
I don't have that.
Wait, what?
How many senses do you have?
Um... Probably like 30.
Oh, wow.
That's a lot of senses.
That's good sense.
Damn.
Okay, well, Sensei Mumei is the winner for this game! Mumei gets one point!
So right now, the points in total... IRyS has no points.
You didn't have to say that! You didn't have to say that!
I still have two points. Mumei has one point. Bae has one point.
Wait, am I really the only one that doesn't have any points?
No, no, no. Fauna also doesn't have a point yet.
We're together! We're together! It's okay. It's okay, because there's still one more game.
Also, this could change everything. It could change everything.
We don't know.
We don't know. We have no idea. We really don't.
On to the last game! On to the last skill!
All right, everybody, it is time for our last game!
Yes! Last game!
Last game! Yay! Oh, this is so much fun!
But I still have zero points.
Well, this is your chance!
What chance? Chance? There's a chance? There's chances with...
Tug of War!
I am amazing at tug of war. I mean, you've never you've never seen it before.
Let me explain the rules here. Okay, when it's your turn, you have the chance to challenge somebody. Okay, one member to play against, okay?
Whoever loses the tug of war will fall into space, into the void. The void makes its return. And whoever wins will get all of the points from the person they won against.
What? All of their points? All of their points?
Wait. What was the point of all the other games then? It's all pointless!
Anyways, so we have to figure out who goes first. How are we going to figure that out?
Maybe we should do the weakest person gets to choose.
IRyS! IRyS!
You said that way too fast!
Well, she's right next to me. Excuse me, she looks pretty weak.
Excuse me? I mean, noodle arms and everything.
I may stand at home, but I actually have hidden muscles all over my my arms.
Yeah, please show us. I will show you guys.
Okay, who's the winner? Who's the winner so far? So far, who's winning?
Kronii?
Kronii.
Ah, no. No, no, no, no, no.
Come here! Come here! Don't touch me! Come here! I've got no business!
Noodle-Rys will show you guys.
You called yourself noodle-Rys.
I'm Udon-Rys.
Because Udon is is much stronger than regular noodle. Okay.
Oh, oh, I see. Okay.
All right. Well, if you make fun of me and you lose, you're going to be you're going to be like so mad. Okay.
Oh, the true test has begun! You guys ready? Ready, ready? Yeah.
Okay. Ready? Ready? Set? Go!
That's what you get for the underdog.
Okay.
So IRyS wins!
I got that muscle right here, look.
Nice!
Okay, who wants to go next?
Who wants to challenge the winner?
I'm feeling pretty confident.
I think I can take you on, IRyS.
You have the guts, I'll ap- I applaud you for that, but...
You have the guts, I applaud you for that, but...
...you, you, you, you...
...you, you, you...
You're like lettuce, you're like salad.
You're so easy to rip up! You're so salad!
That's fighting words! Trash talking!
Fauna, are you ready?
I'm ready.
Any final words?
Prepare to die, IRyS.
Prepare to, for me to rip your sal- salad...
Prepare to, for me to rip your sal— salad...
You can keep trying, you can keep trying.
Ready? Set? Go!
Go! Go! Go! Go!
I died, IRyS.
So Fauna has put IRyS into her place as the weakest.
That's what you get for talking about my salad!
Or one of the weakest, I guess.
I might as well up against Fauna.
Civilization versus nature.
Who will win?
The battle of the age.
Okay, let's go.
You, you can say it.
Fauna, you ready? Battle stance.
Any, any trash tol— I mean, pre-game trash talk?
Your leaves look like they're wilting.
Why is everyone talking about my leaves today?
I'm going to develop a complex.
Your face is nice.
Oh, your face is pretty nice too.
Okay, let's get into it.
No, no. Ready, set, go!
Go!
Come on!
In the end, nature prevails.
Oh, my goodness.
It all comes back to nature.
I guess so, I guess so.
Okay.
Alright, who has— anyone who hasn't gone? Okay.
I guess I will challenge...
Oh, let's go.
Take care.
I'm here to defend my salad today.
You got nothing about your salad! Or words about my salad too!
Your salad.
Your salad's on the line.
Go!
Alright, are you two ready?
Are you ready? Ready?
Are you ready?
Set?
Go!
Some wilty salad right there.
Let's see it.
It went bad.
It rotted.
Even though anyone been keeping count of points?
Well, whoever won.
So you have the most points, yeah, everybody's points now.
Alright, so...
Kronii didn't get to choose, IRyS chose her.
We're not Kronii's choice.
Chance? Who's? You?
We can't, Kronii's chance?
Kronii, your only option, you have no choice. Your only option...
...is Bae, if you want to win, if you want to win.
Unless you don't want to win. If you don't want to win, then...
You can choose, you can choose Bae.
Is this fair though?
Cuz she's like, I guess you're the weakest now.
I want to— I want to choose you.
I want a rematch.
It makes no sense.
I want— I want a rematch.
You want—
You have— Bae is going to win.
Bae's going to win.
Bae's going to win. You have to get your— get your points.
Try to get your points. Try to get your points. Try, try, try.
If you beat her, technically that means I'm the strongest still.
Okay.
So Kronii beat her. That's why.
I always— I really liked you, Kronii. I— I still— I still really like you.
And, you know...
Maybe you can like— does it make you weak at the knees? I don't know.
Looking at you, I'm like weak at the knees.
The only person who can put me at my knees is Kronii, yeah? Not you, I'm sorry.
I tried.
Okay. Okay.
Hey, you guys ready?
Yep.
All right.
Finale.
Ready?
Set?
Go!
Where did that come from?!
Kronii!
Oh!
Okay, maybe, maybe Kronii is not the weakest.
Maybe she is the strongest.
Okay, wait, wait, we have something to prove.
Wait, wait, wait, wait.
Oh yeah. Okay.
Everybody calm down, calm down.
Okay.
That concludes the game.
It's time to go to the next stage.
Oh yeah.
The final stage!
To find the results!
Results of who won!
Everyone's game! Yeah!
And it is time to announce the final score!
We have reached the end of the Promise games.
Already?
Ready!
I know, such a shame. Man, man, man.
But to help announce the results, we're going to bring back...
A-chan!
Yay! I'm here!
Feed me, feed me! Feed me, feed me!
Thank you! Haha!
Okay, the championship of the bully-fost Promise games...
Drum roll, drum roll, drum roll...
Okay, Kronii, you are the winner!
Ouro Kronii!
Wait, did you say I'm coming? I didn't even say that coming stream is for everyone.
Oh no, this is a surprise.
This is a surprise? Okay, it's a crazy game.
Okay, as the championship, Kronii will be awarded a special trophy.
A special trophy?
Wait, what do you mean, a trophy? Excuse me?
I wanted it harder! I wanted it harder!
That's why it was all for laughs and fun!
I know!
Okay, here it is!
Where? Where?
Oh!
Who's up there?
Who's up there? Where is it?
Can I get one too?
Is it me? No, wait, wait, no, no, not me. Ouro Kronii. Oh, thank you. Thank you.
Wait, yeah, how does it what is what kind of trophy is it?
Kronii has won this officially made...
Yagoo trophy! Is that? Mr. Yagoo trophy!
It's all right, you can keep it, Bae.
Is he shirtless? Shirtless? Huh?
He been hitting the gym. Yeah, he built.
Is he a belt? Oh my god. He looks tan.
Damn, everything.
Really cute. How cute it is, right?
Now, let's have a word from the champion, Bae. Yes, please, Bae.
Speech, speech, speech, speech, speech, speech.
Okay, well, first of all, I would like to thank me, myself and I. And um...
It's it's just not a surprise, but I would like to thank that it is a surprise for many of you. Um... Though it isn't... Though it isn't for me, honestly, but you know...
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
It's an honor. Okay, okay. It's an honor. It's an honor. I am very happy to have another trophy added to my collection, my never ending collection. And thank you so much.
I mean, I guess we should... We're good sports. Yeah, we're good sports.
Omedetou! Omedetou! Omedetou! Arigatou!
Yeah, thank you so, Omedetou. Nice Tinder Shinji boys.
Okay, um, anyway, what are you girls going to do after this?
After this? Yeah. There's more? There's more? Yes, there's more. What? What? We're going to do...
A live show!
You guys ready to get hyped? There's still a lot more to come.
We're going to go get ready for the show now. We're going to go to stage, so everybody, off stage right!
We'll see you guys in a bit! Bye-bye!
Bye-bye! Bye-bye!
Bye-bye! I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm alone!
I'm alone, I feel sad.
Enjoy watching the live! Bye-bye!
誰かのため流すナミダ
The tears you shed for someone...
祈りのように頬に伝う
run down your cheeks like a prayer.
それを“弱さ”と隠さないで
Don't hide them away as weakness,
“やさしさ”と受け入れてて
accept them as kindness instead.
呼吸さえも忘れさせる
Making you forget to even breathe,
瞳の中にみつけた空
the sky reflected in your eyes...
太陽だけが輝いている
only the sun is shining.
何を捜し続ける?
What are you searching for?
鏡をみつめ 誓ったあの日
On that day you gazed in the mirror and vowed,
あなたにはきっと見えてた
I'm sure you could see...
自分の背中にも翼があると
that you, too, have wings on your back.
あなたが変わり 世界が変わる
You change, and the world changes.
夢に届け 愛の炎
Let the flames of love reach your dreams,
ゆらゆら蜃気楼 超えて
passing over the swaying mirages.
空にはヒカリ 大地に水を
Light for the sky, water for the earth,
その心に 強さを
and strength for your heart...
未来へたどりつく ANGELUS
reaching out into the future, ANGELUS.
望みがもし叶うのなら
If your wish could be fulfilled,
風になること選ぶでしょう
would you choose to become the wind?
迷いを捨てたあなたの羽根
Throwing away your hesitation,
私の風をつかむ
you catch my wind.
高鳴る胸と 恐れる気持ち
Your throbbing heart and feelings of fear,
痛みが混ざりあう過去を
the past where pain is mixed together—
振り切れたらそこに
once you shake them off,
原色の虹
there is a pure-colored rainbow.
一秒ごとに 世界を変える
Changing the world every second,
刻みだした 愛の鼓動
the pulse of love engraves itself.
ジリジリ燃え上がる 願望
Wishes burning up into flames,
海より深い 見果てぬ夢を
the strength to pursue unfulfilled dreams
追い求める強さが
deeper than the sea,
闇を照らし てゆく ANGELUS
shining upon the darkness, ANGELUS.
走り続けるなら
If you keep on running,
飛び立てるはず
you'll surely be able to fly.
あなたが変わり 世界が変わる
You change, and the world changes.
夢に届け 愛の炎
Let the flames of love reach your dreams,
ゆらゆら蜃気楼 超えて
passing over the swaying mirages.
空にはヒカリ 大地に水を
Light for the sky, water for the earth,
その心に 強さを
and strength for your heart...
未来へたどりつく ANGELUS
reaching out into the future, ANGELUS.
情熱の破片を手にして
Gathering the fragments of passion,
ANGELUS
あなたが変わり 世界が変わる
You change, and the world changes.
夢に届け 愛の炎
Let the flames of love reach your dreams,
ゆらゆら蜃気楼 超えて
passing over the swaying mirages.
空にはヒカリ 大地に水を
Light for the sky, water for the earth,
その心に 強さを
and strength for your heart...
未来へたどりつく ANGELUS
reaching out into the future, ANGELUS.
情熱の破片を手にして
Gathering the fragments of passion,
ANGELUS
誰かのため流すナミダ
The tears flow for someone,
祈りのように頬に伝たう
Like a prayer rolling down my cheeks.
それを“弱さ”と隠さないで
Don't hide that as a "weakness,"
“やさしさ”として受け入れて
Accept it as "kindness."
呼吸さえも忘れさせる
It makes me forget to even breathe.
ぱっつんぱっつん前髪ぱっつん cutie style
Bangs in a cutie style,
やっぱ一直線なら一等賞よ 超すごい！
Straight ahead to first place, super cool!
今日のリップあっち？こっち？そっち？どっち？
Today's lipstick: that? this? that? which?
which? ちょっと！ウォッチ 今何時？
which? Wait! Watch, what time is it?
リンリンリン！ おはよう wake up
Ring, ring, ring! Good morning, wake up,
お・ね・が・い！
Please!
ちょ待って！ ちょ待って！
Wait a minute! Wait a minute!
ring ring ring!
あせらず hurry up
Don't rush, hurry up,
バ・タ・バ・タ☆モーニング
A bustling, busy morning!
リンリンリン！ あわてず make up
Ring, ring, ring! Don't rush, make up,
お・ね・が・い！
Please!
ちょ待って！ ちょ待って！
Wait a minute! Wait a minute!
ring ring ring!
todayは version up
Today is version up,
ド・キ・ド・キ☆モーニング
An exciting morning!
すっぴんすっぴんメガネがヘアピン funny face
Makeup-free with glasses as a hairpin, funny face,
but 3秒待ってね そーこー 変身 超はやい！
But wait 3 seconds, transform super fast!
今日のrapあっち？こっち？そっち？どっち？
Today's rap: that? this? that? which?
which? ちょっと！ウォッチ 今何時？
which? Wait! Watch, what time is it?
知らないフリは キライ！ キライ！
I hate pretending not to know!
知らないセカイ 見 たい！ 見 たい！
I want to see a world I don't know!
4次元 5次元 期待！ 期待！
4th dimension, 5th dimension, expecting it!
10%背伸び したい！ したい！
I want to stretch a bit taller by 10%!
って よね ! ?
Right!?
リンリンリン！ おはよう wake up
Ring, ring, ring! Good morning, wake up,
お・ね・が・い！
Please!
ちょ待って！ ちょ待って！
Wait a minute! Wait a minute!
ring ring ring!
あせらず hurry up
Don't rush, hurry up,
バ・タ・バ・タ☆モーニング
A bustling, busy morning!
リンリンリン！ あわてず make up
Ring, ring, ring! Don't rush, make up,
お・ね・が・い！
Please!
ちょ待って！ ちょ待って！
Wait a minute! Wait a minute!
ring ring ring!
todayは version up
Today is version up,
ド・キ・ド・キ☆モーニング
An exciting morning!
すっぴんすっぴんメガネがヘアピン funny face
Makeup-free with glasses as a hairpin, funny face,
but 3秒待ってね そーこー 変身 超はやい！
But wait 3 seconds, transform super fast!
今日のrapあっち？こっち？そっち？どっち？
Today's rap: that? this? that? which?
which? ちょっと！ウォッチ 今何時？
which? Wait! Watch, what time is it?
知らないフリは キライ！ キライ！
I hate pretending not to know!
知らないセカイ 見 たい！ 見 たい！
I want to see a world I don't know!
4次元 5次元 期待！ 期待！
4th dimension, 5th dimension, expecting it!
10%背伸び したい！ したい！
I want to stretch a bit taller by 10%!
って よね ! ?
Right!?
リンリンリン！ おはよう wake up
Ring, ring, ring! Good morning, wake up,
お・ね・が・い！
Please!
ちょ待って！ ちょ待って！
Wait a minute! Wait a minute!
ring ring ring!
あせらず hurry up
Don't rush, hurry up,
バ・タ・バ・タ☆モーニング
A bustling, busy morning!
リンリンリン！ あわてず make up
Ring, ring, ring! Don't rush, make up,
お・ね・が・い！
Please!
ちょ待って！ ちょ待って！
Wait a minute! Wait a minute!
ring ring ring!
todayは version up
Today is version up,
ド・キ・ド・キ☆モーニング
An exciting morning!
リンリンリン！ おはよう wake up
Ring, ring, ring! Good morning, wake up,
お・ね・が・い！
Please!
ちょ待って！ ちょ待って！
Wait a minute! Wait a minute!
ring ring ring!
あせらず hurry up
Don't rush, hurry up,
バ・タ・バ・タ☆モーニング
A bustling, busy morning!
リンリンリン！ あわてず make up
Ring, ring, ring! Don't rush, make up,
お・ね・が・い！
Please!
ちょ待って！ ちょ待って！
Wait a minute! Wait a minute!
ring ring ring!
todayは version up
Today is version up,
ド・キ・ド・キ☆モーニング
An exciting morning!
リンリンリン！ おはよう wake up
Ring, ring, ring! Good morning, wake up,
お・ね・が・い！
Please!
ちょ待って！ ちょ待って！
Wait a minute! Wait a minute!
ring ring ring!
あせらず hurry up
Don't rush, hurry up,
バ・タ・バ・タ☆モーニング
A bustling, busy morning!
リンリンリン！ あわてず make up
Ring, ring, ring! Don't rush, make up,
お・ね・が・い！
Please!
ちょ待って！ ちょ待って！
Wait a minute! Wait a minute!
ring ring ring!
todayは version up
Today is version up,
ド・キ・ド・キ☆モーニング
An exciting morning!
We did back-to-back songs!
IRyS and I, we performed Angelus.
It was so sexy!
And we were melting and...
And we sang Doki Doki Morning, what did you guys think?
That was... my goodness, that was just so hot, yeah!
I really hope everyone enjoyed the songs as well.
But it is time for... chill and merge!
Pretty showcase starting with, for now,
I'm Fauna!
I have to show off for you the Sap-Ring smartphone ring,
an object which I personally have found very useful.
Stick it on the back of your phone, any phone, and use it to stand up your phone, watch YouTube, watch your hololive...
Wherever you are, wherever you go, you'll have a stand.
And it's in the cute shape of a sapling!
And next is me, what's up?
Yes, so have you ever wanted me to hug you?
Well, I will never do that.
But you can imagine yourself being hugged by getting yourself Warden's Capeley Embrace.
Look like my cape, it's going to be great, go get it!
Yeah, who's next? Mumei!
Oh, hi!
I have here my silicone lantern, you can matchy matchy with me.
We can be twinsies, and it can light up the darkness in your life...
Or can light up whatever is lurking in the shadows!
Yeah, get it! Get it, baby, baby!
Do you ever feel like you have nothing in your wardrobe
because all your t-shirts suck? Don't worry!
I got you the Street Rat T-shirt! We have the same logo,
we can match, and it goes with the snapback and all your other merch,
like your bag and stuff.
Hey, yeah, get it, ayo! Yeah, yeah!
And that's not it, because we have the usual, the usual you would never expected though even though it's the usual...
The acrylic stand!
I promise the 3D poses, they are much bigger than the usual acrylic stands and look really nice together.
So you better get the whole set. It's going to look amazing!
Yeah, you all love CouncilRyS promise, yeah.
Did everyone enjoy CouncilRyS first-class stream?
I'm so happy to be here with you girls, with CouncilRyS!
We promise you many more fun times to come. Yes, that's a promise, right?
A great future, right?
That means, guys, we're actually running out of time!
No!
Looks like we have to... We have to go, you guys. No...
We've been having so much fun!
Are you asking what I think you're asking?
Encore! Encore! Encore! Encore! Encore! Encore! Encore! Encore!
Right, I guess we have time for one more song! Here we go! Yeah!
All right, let's go!
We are Fighting Dreamers
高みを目指して
Aiming high
Fighting Dreamers
なりふり構わず
Don't care what people think about them
Fighting Dreamers
信じるがままに
Follow what they believe
Oli Oli Oli Oh-!
Just go my way!
Right here Right now (Bang!)
ぶっ放せ Like a 弾丸ライナー!
Hit it straight like a line drive!
Right here Right now (Burn!)
ぶっ斬ってくぜ Get the fire!
We're gonna do it and do our best!
Right here Right now (Bang!)
ぶっ放せ Like a 弾丸ライナー!
Hit it straight like a line drive!
Right here Right now (Burn!)
ぶっ斬ってくぜ Get the fire!
We're gonna do it and do our best!
険しい修羅の道の中
Fighting along the way
人脈の地図を広げてどこへ行く?
Where do you think you are going following someone else's map?
極彩色のからすがそれを奪い取って破り捨てた
An insightful crow comes along to tear up the map
さあ心の目 見開いて しかと今を見極めろ!
Now open your eyes and take a look at the truth!
失うモノなんてないさ いざ参らん!
There is nothing to lose so let's go!!!
We are Fighting Dreamers
高みを目指して
Aiming high
Fighting Dreamers
なりふり構わず
Don't care what people think about them
Fighting Dreamers
信じるがままに
Follow what they believe
Oli Oli Oli Oh-!
Just go my way!
Right here Right now (Bang!)
ぶっ放せ Like a 弾丸ライナー!
Hit it straight like a line drive!
Right here Right now (Burn!)
ぶっ斬ってくぜ Get the fire!
We're gonna do it and do our best!
Right here Right now (Bang!)
ぶっ放せ Like a 弾丸ライナー!
Hit it straight like a line drive!
Right here Right now (Burn!)
ぶっ斬ってくぜ Get the fire!
We're gonna do it and do our best!
音を立てず忍び寄る影が
A shadow creeps up without a sound
いつも僕らを惑わせる
And it always leads us astray
有言実行大きな風がうねりを上げて吹き荒れる
True to its word, a high wind swells up and rages around
We are Fighting Dreamers
高みを目指して
Aiming high,
Fighting Dreamers なりふり構わず
Fighting Dreamers, no matter what,
Fighting Dreamers 信じるがままに
Fighting Dreamers, following our beliefs.
Oli Oli Oli Oh-!
Just go my way!
Right here Right now (Bang!)
ぶっ放せ Like a 弾丸ライナー!
Fire away like a bullet liner!
Right here Right now (Burn!)
ぶったたき込め Get the fire!
Strike hard and get the fire!
険しい修羅の道の中
Along the harsh path of Asura,
他人の地図を広げて何処へ行く?
Where are you going with someone else's map?
極彩色心の眼 見開いて
Open wide the eyes of your heart
確と真実を見極めろ! (Yeah!)
and discern the absolute truth! (Yeah!)
失うモノなんてないさ
There's nothing to lose,
いざ参らん!
so let's go now!
We are Fighting Dreamers
高みを目指して
Aiming high,
Fighting Dreamers なりふり構わず
Fighting Dreamers, no matter what,
Fighting Dreamers 信じるがままに
Fighting Dreamers, following our beliefs.
Oli Oli Oli Oh-!
Just go my way!
Right here Right now (Bang!)
ぶっ放せ Like a 弾丸ライナー!
Fire away like a bullet liner!
Right here Right now (Burn!)
ぶったたき込め Get the fire!
Strike hard and get the fire!
音を立てず忍び寄る影が
A shadow creeps up without a sound,
いつも僕らを惑わせる
always leading us astray.
有言実行大きな風が
True to its word, a powerful wind
うねりを上げて吹き荒れる
swells up and rages around.
かざした鋭い刀で
Hold a sharp sword up high
己の未来切り開け! (Yeah!)
and cut open your own future! (Yeah!)
保証なんてどこにもないさ
There are no guarantees anywhere,
なぁそうだろう!?
am I right?!
We are Fighting Dreamers
高みを目指して
Aiming high,
Fighting Dreamers なりふり構わず
Fighting Dreamers, no matter what,
Fighting Dreamers 信じるがままに
Fighting Dreamers, following our beliefs.
Oli Oli Oli Oh-!
Just go my way!
Right here Right now (Bang!)
ぶっ放せ Like a 弾丸ライナー!
Fire away like a bullet liner!
Right here Right now (Burn!)
ぶったたき込め Get the fire!
Strike hard and get the fire!
We are fighting Dreamers この仲間達と
We are Fighting Dreamers, me and my buds,
Fighting Dreamers 全てを巻き込み
Fighting Dreamers, getting everyone involved,
Fighting Dreamers 志高く
Fighting Dreamers, with high aspirations,
Oli Oli Oli Oh-!
We are Fighting Dreamers
高みを目指して
Aiming high,
Fighting Dreamers なりふり構わず
Fighting Dreamers, no matter what,
Fighting Dreamers 信じるがままに
Fighting Dreamers, following our beliefs.
Oli Oli Oli Oh-! Just go my way!
Don't forget your first impulse ever
Let's keep your adventurous ever
let's keep your adventurous spirit ever!
Right here Right now (Bang!)